

## **SKILLS**

#### Skill group

Project Management Creative Design Innovative Programming



#### **Hobbies**

Editing Sketching Photography Design Ui/Ux Coding



#### Languages

Sinhala English



## CONTACT

- A Pitipana North, Homagama
- **\** +94 712 435 202
- ✓ lahiruprasangika2018@gmail.co m
- https://about.me/codeshowlapz
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/lahir u-senavirathna-39b11a215/
- ★ https://twitter.com/LahiruSenavir a5?s=09
- https://www.youtube.com/@Cod eShowLapZ
- nttps://github.com/SE-LAPS

# LAHIRU SENAVIRATHNA

MOBILE APPLICATION DEVELOPER

## **PROFILE**

Junior Software Engineer (Undergraduate) specialising in front end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic java projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including Java, python, PHP, JavaScript, Dart and MySQL. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

## **EXPERIENCE**

2020 - Present

## Freelancing

Web and Mobile App Developer, Colombo

- Apps and Web Interface Design
- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Developing project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.

2022 - present

#### YouTube

This channel offers a diverse programming portfolio, with playlists covering a wide range of programming languages and technologies, from C# to React, Java to Python, and more. This variety ensures that viewers can explore multiple facets of the programming world and find content that aligns with their interests and career goals.

### **EDUCATION**

2021 - present

**Faculty Of Computing** 

NSBM Green University, Colombo B.Sc Software Engineering

2018 to 2021

**Faculty Of Computing** 

University Of Pearson, Kandy
B Tech HIND Software Engineering

2018

**Education/course name** 

• Passed G.C.E(A/L) Mathematics stream in 2018( I:N-2987724)

2012

#### Education/course name

Organization, City

• Passed G.C.E(O/L) in 2012(I:N-23216948)

## **COURSE**

Java Framework (certificate): Sololearn, Udemy, Hackerrank.

Programming Languages: Java, JavaScript, Python, PHP, C, C++, MySQL.

## **VOLUNTEER WORK**

#### **NSBM GREEN UNIVERSITY**

IEEE Volunteer | 2021 - present

- "Road To Full Stack-Mobile" organized by IEEE WIE student branch affinity group of NSBM is a great opportunity for you to begin the strategy of mobile application development.
- "Duothan" 2.0 organized by IEEE student branch of NSBM in collaboration with IEEE WIE student affinity group of NSBM and IEEE of NSBM successfully held on 23 February 2022.
- "Arduino competition" for Arduino week celebration organized by IEEE student branch of NSBM in collaboration with FUSION 2022.

#### **NSBM GREEN UNIVERSITY**

CSSE & FOSS Volunteer | 2022 - present

- "How to build your IT career during an economic crisis" great webinar organized by the FOSS Community of NSBM.
- "ESTHETIQUE '21" the UI/UX workshop organized by FOSS NSBM together with WIF NSBM.
- "HashCode" awareness session FOSS NSBM successfully held on 20 February 2022.

## **REFERENCES**

#### 01) Ms.K.K. Pavithra Subashini

, Senior Lecturer / Head Faculty of Computing NSBM Green University . pavithras@nsbm.ac.lk +94 776 181 390

#### 02) Mr.A.B.Senavirathna

, Lead software Engineer at IFS asankabandaraifs1@gmail.co m

+94 775 557 487

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Name

S.G.M.L.P.Senavirathna

**Birthdate** 10/02/1996

**Gender** Male

**Residence** Homagama

**Nationality** Sinhala

#### **END**

I hereby attest that the above information is true & correct according to the best of my knowledge.

Senavirathna	30/11/2023
Signature	Date